Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1997 March-1997 April; DVD (Disc 104)
    - Nuclear testing deception, 1997 April 2 (Video 23)
    - Thanks, Utah Senators, 1997 April 3 (Video 24)
    - Electric utilities deregulate, 1997 April 4 (Video 25)
    - Water rates increase, 1997 April 7 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view: Tricia Call, re rural Utah taxes, 1997 April 8 (Video 27)
    - Council for exceptional children, 1997 April 9 (Video 28)
    - Higher education governance, 1997 April 10 (Video 29)
    - Road repairs everywhere, 1997 April 11 (Video 30)
    - Changing the I.R.S., 1997 April 14 (Video 31)
    - Prevention or treatment, 1997 April 15 (Video 32)
    - Arch L. Madsen, 1997 April 16 (Video 33)
    - College and technology, 1997 April 17 (Video 34)
    - America's arms race, 1997 April 18 (Video 35)
    - Organ donor week, 1997 April 21 (Video 36)
    - Another point of view: Christ Cannon, re balanced budget amendment, 1997 April 22 (Video 37)
    - Secretaries deserve honors, 1997 April 23 (Video 38)
    - Secrecy and privacy, 1997 April 24 (Video 39)
    - Doctor or provider, 1997 April 25 (Video 40)
    - The trail west, 1997 April 28 (Video 41)
    - Moment of laughter, 1997 April 29 (Video 42)
    - More I.N.S. agents, 1997 April 30 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1997 May-1997 June; DVD (Disc 105)
    - Utah Safety Month, 1997 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Davis county schools, 1997 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Thanks, John Hart, 1997 May 5 (Video 3)
    - KSL at 75, 1997 May 6 (Video 4)
    - Another point of viwe: Larry Rupp, re water rate increases, 1997 May 7 (Video 5)
    - Cheating on the internet, 1997 May 8 (Video 6)
    - Conference on volunteers, 1997 May 9 (Video 7)
    - Chess and computers, 1997 May 12 (Video 8)
    - Diversity in schools, 1997 May 13 (Video 9)
    - Seperatists deserve scorn, 1997 May 14 (Video 10)
    - City and the olympics, 1997 May 15 (Video 11)
    - Older Americans Month, 1997 May 16 (Video 12)
    - Board ousts Pingree, 1997 May 19 (Video 13)
    - Attack commericals misfire, 1997 May 20 (Video 14)
    - Dimple Dell bridge, 1997 May 21 (Video 15)
    - Tribune sold to T.C.I., 1997 May 22 (Video 16)
    - Traffic slowdowns increase, 1997 May 23 (Video 17)
    - Balancing the budget, 1997 May 26 (Video 18)
    - Wise use of testing, 1997 May 27 (Video 19)
    - Deseret news building, 1997 May 28 (Video 20)
    - Salt saves lives, 1997 May 29 (Video 21)
    - Two wrongs and right, 1997 May 30 (Video 22)
    - Abravanel Hall mistake, 1997 June 2 (Video 23)
    - More Guadalupe schools, 1997 June 3 (Video 24)
    - Graduation time, 1997 June 4 (Video 25)
    - Crime rate drops, 1997 June 5 (Video 26)
    - Cuba needs light, 1997 June 6 (Video 27)
    - Child Advocate Award, 1997 June 9 (Video 28)
    - West desert high, 1997 June 10 (Video 29)
    - Diseases of the brain, 1997 June 11 (Video 30)
    - Keeping track of students, 1997 June 12 (Video 31)
    - Hong Kong changes, 1997 June 13 (Video 32)
    - Help flood victims, 1997 June 16 (Video 33)
    - Jazz makes us proud, 1997 June 17 (Video 34)
    - More restrooms needed, 1997 June 18 (Video 35)
    - Digital television ahead, 1997 June 19 (Video 36)
    - Year 2000 problem, 1997 June 20 (Video 37)
    - Tobacco money suspect, 1997 June 23 (Video 38)
    - Another point of view: Brent Overson, re Abravanel Hall, 1997 June 24 (Video 39)
    - Summer travel time, 1997 June 25 (Video 40)
    - Hansen Planetarium move, 1997 June 26 (Video 41)
    - Road worry reality, 1997 June 27 (Video 42)
    - McVeigh death sentence, 1997 June 30 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1997 July-1997 August; DVD (Disc 106)
    - Another point of view: David Wegner, re Glen Canyon Dam, 1997 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Respect and Utah, 1997 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Amtrak wants money, 1997 July 3 (Video 3)
    - Fourth of July, 1997 July 4 (Video 4)
    - Sports and unity, 1997 July 7 (Video 5)
    - Poverty not inevitable, 1997 July 8 (Video 6)
    - Wagons in the parade, 1997 July 9 (Video 7)
    - Jelesnik writes a book, 1997 July 10 (Video 8)
    - Puerto Rico statehood, 1997 July 11 (Video 9)
    - Conversation about race, 1997 July 14 (Video 10)
    - Another point of view: James Johnson, re Dimple Dell bridge, 1997 July 15 (Video 11)
    - Crime summit success, 1997 July 16 (Video 12)
    - After the olympics, 1997 July 17 (Video 13)
    - The bug is back, 1997 July 18 (Video 14)
    - Week of history, 1997 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Utah Historical Society, 1997 July 22 (Video 16)
    - Another Utah milestone, 1997 July 23 (Video 17)
    - Days of '47, 1997 July 24 (Video 18)
    - Building on the past, 1997 July 25 (Video 19)
    - City council grandstands, 1997 July 28 (Video 20)
    - Medicare means test, 1997 July 29 (Video 21)
    - Take it easy, 1997 July 30 (Video 22)
    - Art support survives, 1997 July 31 (Video 23)
    - Rural needs ignored, 1997 August 1 (Video 24)
    - Power and fame, 1997 August 4 (Video 25)
    - Complaints by letter, 1997 August 5 (Video 26)
    - Airport parking fees, 1997 August 6 (Video 27)
    - End whitewater probe, 1997 August 7 (Video 28)
    - Thanks to visitors, 1997 August 8 (Video 29)
    - Pedestrian friendly city, 1997 August 11 (Video 30)
    - Prison numbers alarming, 1997 August 12 (Video 31)
    - Balanced budget news, 1997 August 13 (Video 32)
    - Traffic control advice, 1997 August 14 (Video 33)
    - Smart card technology, 1997 August 15 (Video 34)
    - Water wars begin, 1997 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Philo T. Farnsworth, 1997 August 19 (Video 36)
    - Welch and the olympics, 1997 August 20 (Video 37)
    - Child-proof lids, 1997 August 21 (Video 38)
    - Utah's work force, 1997 August 22 (Video 39)
    - Tough on gangs, 1997 August 25 (Video 40)
    - There they go again, 1997 August 26 (Video 41)
    - County government plan, 1997 August 27 (Video 42)
    - Affirmative action needed, 1997 August 28 (Video 43)
    - Baseball's death wish, 1997 August 29 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1997 September-1997 October; DVD (Disc 107)
    - Labor Day, 1997 September 1 (Video 1)
    - Back to hot schools, 1997 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Don't blame workers, 1997 September 3 (Video 3)
    - Protect danger cave, 1997 September 4 (Video 4)
    - Grandparents Day, 1997 September 5 (Video 5)
    - Legacy of Diana, 1997 September 8 (Video 6)
    - Story telling festival, 1997 September 9 (Video 7)
    - G.I.F.T. conferences set, 1997 September 10 (Video 8)
    - Olympics in good hands, 1997 September 11 (Video 9)
    - Land mine dangers, 1997 September 12 (Video 10)
    - Capable work force, 1997 September 15 (Video 11)
    - Help a neighbor, 1997 September 16 (Video 12)
    - Constitution week, 1997 September 17 (Video 13)
    - Air Force reserve, 1997 September 18 (Video 14)
    - Nuclear fuel storage, 1997 September 19 (Video 15)
    - Financing your education, 1997 September 22 (Video 16)
    - Internet and the schools, 1997 September 23 (Video 17)
    - Small adjustments needed, 1997 September 24 (Video 18)
    - Stop the feuding, 1997 September 25 (Video 19)
    - Food safety remedy, 1997 September 26 (Video 20)
    - Conflict with wisdom, 1997 September 29 (Video 21)
    - Politics and the census, 1997 September 30 (Video 22)
    - Join school testing, 1997 October 1 (Video 23)
    - Stop internet gambling, 1997 October 2 (Video 24)
    - Blame El Nino, 1997 October 3 (Video 25)
    - Crime rate realities, 1997 October 6 (Video 26)
    - Fixing the I.R.S., 1997 October 7 (Video 27)
    - National Children's Day, 1997 October 8 (Video 28)
    - Value of private prisons, 1997 October 9 (Video 29)
    - Campaign cost realities, 1997 October 10 (Video 30)
    - Veto hits home, 1997 October 13 (Video 31)
    - Olympics not the cause, 1997 October 14 (Video 32)
    - Hotel room boom, 1997 October 15 (Video 33)
    - United Way campaign, 1997 October 16 (Video 34)
    - College campus parking, 1997 October 17 (Video 35)
    - Fiction of campaign reform, 1997 October 20 (Video 36)
    - Another point of viwe: Reese Hunter, re smart card, 1997 October 21 (Video 37)
    - Travel habits change, 1997 October 22 (Video 38)
    - County government change, 1997 October 23 (Video 39)
    - Utah partnership honored, 1997 October 24 (Video 40)
    - Winter without shelter, 1997 October 27 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view: Dianne Nielson, re nuclear waste storage, 1997 October 28 (Video 42)
    - Plan for growth, 1997 October 29 (Video 43)
    - Approve recreation bonds, 1997 October 30 (Video 44)
    - Freeway landscape important, 1997 October 31 (Video 45)
  - KSL editorials, 1997 November-1997 December; DVD (Disc 108)
    - Stock market swings, 1997 November 3 (Video 1)
    - Listen to warnings, 1997 November 4 (Video 2)
    - A personal message, 1997 November 5 (Video 3)
    - Auto tax sensible, 1997 November 6 (Video 4)
    - Think and drive, 1997 November 7 (Video 5)
    - Power of one, 1997 November 10 (Video 6)
    - Measuring college performance, 1997 November 11 (Video 7)
    - Banks vs. credit unions, 1997 November 12 (Video 8)
    - Winter road woes, 1997 November 13 (Video 9)
    - Decimals win again, 1997 November 14 (Video 10)
    - Legislature long enough, 1997 November 17 (Video 11)
    - The China threat, 1997 November 18 (Video 12)
    - Campaign reform fails, 1997 November 19 (Video 13)
    - Street damage extensive, 1997 November 20 (Video 14)
    - Three, two, ace, 1997 November 21 (Video 15)
    - Saddam Hussein again, 1997 November 24 (Video 16)
    - Airbag safety changes, 1997 November 25 (Video 17)
    - Thanksgiving, 1997 November 26 (Video 18)
    - On being thankful, 1997 November 27 (Video 19)
    - A city of beauty, 1997 November 28 (Video 20)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1997 December 1 (Video 21)
    - Community services council, 1997 December 2 (Video 22)
    - Drug control challenge, 1997 December 3 (Video 23)
    - C.I.A. needs review, 1997 December 4 (Video 24)
    - Hatch image bruised, 1997 December 5 (Video 25)
    - Improve day-care quality, 1997 December 8 (Video 26)
    - Corradini keeps moving, 1997 December 9 (Video 27)
    - Children imitate adults, 1997 December 10 (Video 28)
    - Surrounded by miracles, 1997 December 11 (Video 29)
    - Making english official, 1997 December 12 (Video 30)
    - Guns and reason, 1997 December 15 (Video 31)
    - Paper, paper, everywhere, 1997 December 16 (Video 32)
    - School route planning, 1997 December 17 (Video 33)
    - This is your life, 1997 December 18 (Video 34)
    - Commuter rail plans, 1997 December 19 (Video 35)
    - Christmas and Hanukkah, 1997 December 22 (Video 36)
    - Testing and competition, 1997 December 23 (Video 37)
    - Christmas Eve, 1997 December 24 (Video 38)
    - Christmas Day, 1997 December 25 (Video 39)
    - Short history of transportation, 1997 December 26 (Video 40)
    - Nation of complainers, 1997 December 29 (Video 41)
    - Microsoft and competition, 1997 December 30 (Video 42)
    - New Year's Eve, 1997 December 31 (Video 43)
    - New Year's Day, 1998 January 1 (Video 44)
    - An editorial farewell, 1998 January 2 (Video 45)
  - Utah Broadcasters Association "Hall of Fame", 2010 May 11; DVD (Disc 109)
    Induction of Don Gale. Hosted at University of Utah.
  - Words, words, words, undated; DVD (Disc 110)
    Twenty years of Don Gale's history, humor, and editorial comment. Directed by Michael Gale, son of Don Gale. Produced by Don Gale.
- Izzi Wagner tributes, 1938-2004
  - I.J. Wagner visit to Hollywood, 1938; DVD (Disc 1)
    Video transfer from 16mm film taken by I.J. Wagner during a visit to Hollywood in 1938.
  - I.J. Wagner speech to executives of Skaggs Drug Company, 1967 June 05; DVD (Disc 2)
  - I.J. Wagner: 1996 Man of the Year, 1996 October 03; DVD (Disc 3)
    Man of the year award presented by the Utah Arthritis Foundation
  - I.J. Wagner's 89th birthday, 2004 March 31; DVD (Disc 4)
    Birthday party at Granato's, reported by Chris Vanocur of KTVX Channel 4.
  - I.J. "Izzi" Wagner: A brief look back, undated; DVD (Disc 5)
  - Essence of Rose, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 6)